Register of the Willy Achim Fiedler papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Videorecording, 1993 September 10 (Box 15)
  "A Conversation with Willie Fiedler," VHS videocassette.
- Photographs, 1953-1959, undated
  - Naval Air Missile Test Center (NAMTC)
    - Miscellaneous award ceremonies, 1953-1956 (Box-folder 16: 1)
    - Distinguished Civilian Service Award ceremony, 1954 February 23 (Box-folder 16: 2)
    - U.S. citizenship ceremony, 1954 December 10 (Box-folder 16: 3)
    - Split Aircraft Wing patent, 1956 April 19 (Box-folder 16: 4)
      See also: Career File/Patents/Split Aircraft Wing.
    - Navy's Superior Accomplishment Award ceremony, 1957 April 29 (Box-folder 16: 5)
    - Missiles, 1954-1957 (Box-folder 16: 6)
      Includes Loon and Regulus missiles.
    - Hunter's Point, undated (Box-folder 16: 7)
  - Lockheed Missiles and Space Company
    - Experiments, undated (Box-folder 16: 8)
    - Equipment, 1959 June 9-July 20, undated (Box-folder 16: 9)
    - Missiles, undated (Box-folder 16: 10)
      Includes the Polaris Missile.
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 16: 11)
      Includes portraits of Fiedler and photographs of the Lockheed grounds.
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box-folder 16: 12-13)
    Folder 12 includes photos of the Fi 256 plane, a group of WWII German officers, the John J. Montgomery award ceremony, and Fiedler with Manfred Hensel. Folder 13 includes photos of various unidentified planes and missiles.
- Oversize Material, 1936-1988, undated
  - Blueprints, 1956-1970, undated (Box-folder 17: 1, Map case)
    Related to the development of Polaris, Modular Multipurpose Missiles, underwater launch, weapons systems, and sub designs. See also: Career File/Projects/Lockheed Missiles and Space Company.
  - Experiment charts, 1988 (Box-folder 17: 2-3)
    Data charts on alpha decay for projects conducted with William Barker of Altran Corporation. See also: Career File/Projects/Altran Corporation.
  - Diagrams, 1980, undated (Box-folder 17: 4)
    Related to the development of missile capsules, sub designs, Trident II, and Modular Multipurpose Missiles. See also: Career File/Projects/Northrup Aircraft Inc., Lockheed Missiles and Space Company, and Missile Capsules.
  - Graphs and charts, 1987-1988, undated (Box-folder 17: 5)
    Related to projects on shelf deployment, STRAT-X, and alpha decay. See also: Career File/Projects/Lockheed Missiles and Space Company and Altran Corporation, and Subject File/William A. Barker.
  - Miscellaneous, 1962-1974 (Box-folder 17: 6)
    Includes a periodic table of elements, organizational charts of Lockheed's leadership, and a historical map titled, "Segelflug auf der Wasserkuppe." In English and German.
  - Large blueprints, 1936-1950s (Map case)
    See also: Biographical File/Oxnard House Design, and Career File/Projects/British Aircraft Manufacturing Co. Ltd.
  - Large diagrams, 1960s-1980s (Map case)
    See also: Career File/Projects/Gerhard Fieseler Werke and Lockheed Missiles and Space Company. In English and German.